'Til death do they part.
Venom: The Last Dance is a action, science fiction,
adventure film directed by Kelly Marcel.
Eddie and Venom are on the run.
Hunted by both of their worlds and with the net closing in, the duo are forced into a
devastating decision that will bring the curtains down on Venom and Eddie's last dance.
Eddie Brock / Venom, played by Tom Hardy.
Strickland, played by Chiwetel Ejiofor.
Dr. Teddy Paine, played by Juno Temple.
Martin, played by Rhys Ifans.
Detective Mulligan, played by Stephen Graham.
Mrs. Chen, played by Peggy Lu.
Venom: The Last Dance is a 2024 American superhero film
based on the Marvel Comics character Venom.
It is the sequel to Venom (2018) and Venom: Let There Be Carnage (2021),
and the fifth film in Sony's Spider-Man Universe (SSU).
Written and directed by Kelly Marcel, it stars Tom Hardy as Eddie Brock and Venom, alongside
Chiwetel Ejiofor, Juno Temple, Rhys Ifans, Stephen Graham, Peggy Lu, and Alanna Ubach.
In the film, Eddie and Venom are on the run from both of their worlds.
Hardy revealed in August 2018 that he was signed on to appear in a third Venom film and Sony
Pictures began development by December 2021 after the second film was released.
Marcel and Hardy were writing the script by June 2022, and Marcel was set
to make her directorial debut with the film that October.
New cast members, including Ejiofor and Temple, joined in mid-2023
and filming began at the end of June 2023 in Spain.
Production was halted the next month due to the 2023 SAG-AFTRA
strike, and resumed that November after the strike ended.
The film was completed by the end of February 2024 and
its title was revealed a month later.
Venom: The Last Dance premiered at the Regal Times Square theater in New York City on
October 21, 2024, and was released in the United States on October 25.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, with
some praising Hardy's performance.
Despite being the lowest-grossing film in the trilogy, it was still a
box-office success, grossing $478.9 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of hero, superhero, anti
hero, villain, alien life-form.
The tone is thought_provoking.